<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal</title>
    <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:49:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - Libra</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/shooter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:49:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/shooter-2/</guid>
      <description>Every JFK-head knows deep down in their heart of hearts that there is no Truth about the events in Dallas on 11/22. No matter how many volumes of the Warren Commission are devoured, secret files eventually burst into light, or scratchy, lofi recordings surface, there will never be a seamless story we can tell. The Zapruder film emerged after decades in a vault, and this unearthed secret became, instead of objective evidence, nothing more than a Roarshach test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Review - Night Agent</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/nightagent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/nightagent/</guid>
      <description>I’m enthralled by the Night Agent. It’s not a good show, of course. It’s limp, it’s stale bread, it’s a ‘thriller’ without thrills. Yet I am totally enthralled.
My first reaction to it was one of confusion. The series was apparently created by Shawn Ryan, head writer of the widely acclaimed The Shield, a show that follows an LAPD unit stacked with corrupt psychos. It’s just so strange to have created a show steeped in the moral darkness of the police and then create a show with a bewildering amount of love for the FBI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Doctor Strange and the whatever whatever (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/strange/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/strange/</guid>
      <description>I’m always looking to decode the subtle political messages they (I do NOT mean The Jews) are transmitting via blockbuster movies. But a film about how “America” shouldn’t have to give up her “superpower” even though she’s been irresponsible with it? (Accidentally killing her parents / doing Vietnam, Iraq, etc.) Because the other people who might have them would use them even more irresponsibly? (The witch lady / China, etc.) That’s not very fucking subtle at all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Plane (2023)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/plane/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/plane/</guid>
      <description>You’re allowed to clap when this one lands! (7/10)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV Review - Outer Banks</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/outerbanks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/outerbanks/</guid>
      <description>Do you experience the effects of sharply denominated social class boundaries in your daily life? Do you feel that, because you were born into a certain set of economic conditions, you are constantly suppressed, oppressed, and exploited? Well fuck you, loser. You must grind harder. We all have the same 24 hours, and you need to start using yours to hustle faster and chase that bread like your life depends on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spacecraft Review - Voyager 1 and 2</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/voyager/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/voyager/</guid>
      <description>NASA launched a couple of spacecrafts called the Voyager 1 and 2 in the 70s and sent each of them on a path towards the outer reaches of space. They’ve taken some neat pictures and stuff since then, but that isn’t their only purpose. The crafts both hold a golden phonograph record containing sights and sounds of Earth, intended as a time capsule for - or a first step in communicating with - any alien species the Voyagers happen to come across.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - Catch 22</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/catch/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 13:00:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/catch/</guid>
      <description>Tedious. The “Who’s on First” of classic American novels. 0/22</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Braveheart</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/braveheart/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 15:37:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/braveheart/</guid>
      <description>The violence is great. The score is awesome. And whom among us has not pushed the boyfriend of our gay, cowardly son out of a window? It’s not homophobic if the guy is annoying. That’s all fine, but I just think it’s fucked up that we’re supposed to pretend that Mel Gibson is handsome.
Also, now that I’m thinking about it, all the freedom shit that Wallace spouts is kind of muddled, isn’t it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Review - Zucker Hillside Hospital</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/zucker/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 10:29:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/zucker/</guid>
      <description>Friday, December 30th: My roommate’s heart warned him not to eat the food here, but the tray they give me for dinner isn’t so bad. The chicken has some modest seasoning and is not bone dry, which is an improvement from my last stay, and there’s a whole wheat Smucker’s Uncrustable. Although, the tray and the containers themselves are a mishmash of recyclable and non-recyclable materials, all of which go straight into the garbage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - Infinite Jest</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/infinite-jest/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 15:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/infinite-jest/</guid>
      <description>I finished this book the same day I completed my switch to a flip phone. So it was a timely read for me, given that and also given my quest over the past year to become less stimulated. The experience of reading Infinite Jest, the experience of chugging through the never-ending pages and footnotes, shores up a main theme of the novel: that there’s something to be had when you give up the pursuit of pure pleasure and that there’s something actually obscene - maybe even deadly - about indulgent bliss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Avatar: The Way of Water</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/avatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 15:39:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/avatar/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever looked your father in the eye? And told him, the way of water has no beginning and no end?
It’s a movie so earnest you sometimes have to avert your eyes.
It’s 3 hours long, a nature documentary and an action film rolled into one.
And it’s new. It’s actually something new. It’s a mega-blockbuster that doesn’t exclusively rely on nostalgia. It has sprung from James Cameron’s mind like Athena from Zeus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review(s) - Books I didn&#39;t read in high school</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/high-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 15:38:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/high-school/</guid>
      <description>Parable of the Sower - least charismatic teenage girl starts the least interesting religion in the world. 1 trash can.
Brave New World - a British man is very afraid of contraception and pre-marital sex. 2 trash cans
American Pastoral - Am I supposed to give a fuck about this guy? Because I don’t. 3 trash cans.
Moby Dick - Okay, yeah. It’s good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - Giovanni&#39;s Room</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/giovanni/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 15:39:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/giovanni/</guid>
      <description>what kind of life can two men have together, anyway? 10/10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Book Review - The Overstory</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/the-overstory/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 15:39:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/the-overstory/</guid>
      <description>It’s the tree book. We love those trees, don’t we, folks? When I was on twitter - a dark time - I would see people throw around this word: eco-fascism. And at first I was like, y’all are just making shit up now, huh? But it’s probably not what you think. It’s not saying that environmental regulations are fascist or that all vegans are secretly nazis. As far as I could tell, it’s used to describe people who are really into the idea of over-population and de-population (of specific groups, of course) and are big fans of Malthus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Text Message Review - My Father&#39;s &#39;Guidelines&#39;</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2022 10:17:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>I received this text message from my father a long time ago, 2013, 2014, maybe? I had done something wrong, something sinful. I don’t remember what. What I do remember is copying the message - barely reading it - and pasting it into the notes app on my iPhone (that’s, The iPhone, the first one). I remember that I didn’t understand it at the time, and I thought I might understand it later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Bones and All (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bones-and-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 15:28:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bones-and-all/</guid>
      <description>Hmmm, the new American Eagle catalog is kinda weird. 0/10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review - Sinner Get Ready (2021)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/sinner-get-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:24:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/sinner-get-ready/</guid>
      <description>“Sinner, you better get ready / Sinner, you better get ready … Hallelujah”
You’ve been told. It doesn’t matter where you are; the warning of God’s judgement has reached your ears. The billboards can be found anywhere in America and beyond, from the most rural parts of the Bible Belt to the gayest, most liberal cities on the coasts. They interrogate you: “Are you ready to meet Jesus?”
Judgment Day has been near for quite some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Call Me By Your Name (2017)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/cmbyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 15:20:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/cmbyn/</guid>
      <description>The flights to Peru were largely empty back when I worked for Delta. Lima probably wasn’t my first choice of destination that Friday afternoon, but in the end it seemed as good a place as any to spend a weekend (or, more accurately, a Saturday). Coincidentally, someone from my church at the time was on the same flight, going on a mission trip. She was on her way to spiritually colonize the same place I picked for my mini-vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Review - Yosemite National Park</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/yosemite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:25:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/yosemite/</guid>
      <description>I must unfortunately report that the High Line is now worse than Time Square. TS is the infamous former titleholder of Worst Place in New York, once top of the list of Worst Places but now trounced by Soho, Washington Square Park, etc., and now the High Line too, suffering (the High Line is) from the dual annoyance of 1) foreign tourists, impossibly many, impossibly slow, some with strollers, the frequency of the sound of their dumb, throaty, stupid European languages sharply increasing, then decreasing as I push past them, and 2) runners, sweaty runners trying to push past me like a car aggressively overtaking you only to end up at the stoplight right next to you, like who do you think you are buddy - a terrible combo which has the effect of promoting the High Line over TS (but not WSP, dear god no - I mean, the idea of a park where the goal is to be seen is in such bad taste) in the catalog of Worst Places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Bros (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:22:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bros/</guid>
      <description>Billy Eichner seems to have written and starred in a romantic comedy while still being on the fence, in real life, about whether he deserves to be loved or not. Perhaps he should have worked that out beforehand, so watching the movie doesn’t feel like violating patient-therapist confidentiality.
Bros (2022) is a bit of a bait and switch. From the title, I guess I thought it’d be a movie about how funny it is to try to be gay without being “gay”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Decision to Leave (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/decision-to-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 15:11:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/decision-to-leave/</guid>
      <description>Decision to Leave (2022) may have set the South Korean film renaissance back 20 years. When I found out the director of Oldboy and The Handmaiden had come out with a new movie, I was completely willing to entrust him with 2 hours and 18 minutes of my time. Now I’m thinking they gave Park Chan-wook Best Director at Cannes because they all felt bad for him.
The idea that there’s an inherent romance in the cop/suspect relationship is a cool and interesting one, even if the movie that came out of it is a big yawn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
