<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Collateralized Death Obligations</title>
    <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Collateralized Death Obligations</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:33:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Argument for the Reasonableness of Suicide</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/suicide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 15:33:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/suicide/</guid>
      <description>About You This is you:
You are in pain.
Some days you feel okay, occasionally you feel very good, dangerously good, but most days you feel very sad. This sadness is a physical, full-body feeling, accompanied by psychic misery. You can remember feeling this way even when you were very young.
You do your best anyway. You study and get good grades. You work out, eat healthy, and get 8 hours of sleep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advertisement Review - The Overnight Walk</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/overnight-walk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 15:26:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/overnight-walk/</guid>
      <description>“One night. One goal. Stop suicide. June 4th 2022” Though they’re a few months old by now, I still see the posters around town. An overnight walk in support of suicide prevention is a decent metaphor, actually. I’ll give them that. There are people - loved ones - who live in permanent darkness, and the walk is a chance for those who may not be able to understand or relate to commune with the melancholics in the dead of night and into the sunrise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Album Review - Sinner Get Ready (2021)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/sinner-get-ready/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 15:24:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/sinner-get-ready/</guid>
      <description>“Sinner, you better get ready / Sinner, you better get ready … Hallelujah”
You’ve been told. It doesn’t matter where you are; the warning of God’s judgement has reached your ears. The billboards can be found anywhere in America and beyond, from the most rural parts of the Bible Belt to the gayest, most liberal cities on the coasts. They interrogate you: “Are you ready to meet Jesus?”
Judgment Day has been near for quite some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Call Me By Your Name (2017)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/cmbyn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2022 15:20:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/cmbyn/</guid>
      <description>The flights to Peru were largely empty back when I worked for Delta. Lima probably wasn’t my first choice of destination that Friday afternoon, but in the end it seemed as good a place as any to spend a weekend (or, more accurately, a Saturday). Coincidentally, someone from my church at the time was on the same flight, going on a mission trip. She was on her way to spiritually colonize the same place I picked for my mini-vacation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Review - Yosemite National Park</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/yosemite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2022 15:25:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/yosemite/</guid>
      <description>I must unfortunately report that the High Line is now worse than Time Square. TS is the infamous former titleholder of Worst Place in New York, once top of the list of Worst Places but now trounced by Soho, Washington Square Park, etc., and now the High Line too, suffering (the High Line is) from the dual annoyance of 1) foreign tourists, impossibly many, impossibly slow, some with strollers, the frequency of the sound of their dumb, throaty, stupid European languages sharply increasing, then decreasing as I push past them, and 2) runners, sweaty runners trying to push past me like a car aggressively overtaking you only to end up at the stoplight right next to you, like who do you think you are buddy - a terrible combo which has the effect of promoting the High Line over TS (but not WSP, dear god no) in the catalog of Worst Places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Bros (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bros/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 15:22:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/bros/</guid>
      <description>Billy Eichner seems to have written and starred in a romantic comedy while still being on the fence, in real life, about whether he deserves to be loved or not. Perhaps he should have worked that out beforehand, so watching the movie doesn’t feel like violating patient-therapist confidentiality.
Bros (2022) is a bit of a bait and switch. From the title, I guess I thought it’d be a movie about how funny it is to try to be gay without being “gay”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Review - Naval Nuclear Power Training Command</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/nnptc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 14:53:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/nnptc/</guid>
      <description>When you enter into the military, there’s a film of despair over the whole process. The military is often the last resort, as it certainly was for me, and that feeling, the feeling of being on your last leg, that feeling permeates.
The recruiting station for the section of Atlanta covering Georgia Tech was inside South Dekalb Mall on Candler Rd. It’s in not the worst neighborhood in Atlanta, but it’s not good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Movie Review - Decision to Leave (2022)</title>
      <link>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/decision-to-leave/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 15:11:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://dvdk1ng0.github.io/posts/decision-to-leave/</guid>
      <description>Decision to Leave (2022) may have set the South Korean film renaissance back 20 years. When I found out the director of _Oldboy_and The Handmaiden had come out with a new movie, I was completely willing to entrust him with 2 hours and 18 minutes of my time. Now I’m thinking they gave Park Chan-wook Best Director at Cannes because they all felt bad for him.
The idea that there’s an inherent romance in the cop/suspect relationship is a cool and interesting one, even if the movie that came out of it sucks.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
